let questions1 = [
    {
    category: "Paranormal",
    numb: 1,
    question: "Where is the house located in Conjuring 1?",
    answer: "Harrisville",
    options: [
      "Harrisville",
      "Portland",
      "Lexigton",
      "San Francisco"
    ]
  },
    {
    category: "Paranormal",
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the baby's name in Insidious 1?",
    answer: "Cali",
    options: [
      "Cleo",
      "Caroline",
      "Cali",
      "Anna"
    ]
  },
    {
    category: "Paranormal",
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which mythology does the demon in The exorcist comes from?",
    answer: "The babylonian mythology",
    options: [
      "The egyptian mythology",
      "The greek mythology",
      "The nordic mythology",
      "The babylonian mythology"
    ]
  },
    {
    category: "Paranormal",
    numb: 4,
    question: "Why is Rosemary pregnant with the devil in Rosemary's baby?",
    answer: "For her husband's fame",
    options: [
      "For her husband's fame",
      "She believes in Satan",
      "She is part of a cult",
      "It's not explained"
    ]
  },
    {
    category: "Paranormal",
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the main evil object in Occulus?",
    answer: "A mirror",
    options: [
      "A doll",
      "A mirror",
      "A necklace",
      "A ring"
    ]
  }

];

let questions2 = [
    {
    category: "Slasher",
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who is the killer in The Nightmare on Elm Street ?",
    answer: "Freddy Krueger",
    options: [
      "Freddy Krueger",
      "Jason Voorhes",
      "Leatherface",
      "Michael Myers"
    ]
  },
    {
    category: "Slasher",
    numb: 2,
    question: "Where does Friday 13th take place?",
    answer: "In Camp Crystal Lake",
    options: [
      "In Camp Crystal Lake",
      "In Camp Green Lodge",
      "In Camp Tree House",
      "In Camp Night Owl"
    ]
  },
    {
    category: "Slasher",
    numb: 3,
    question: "Where is the opening scene of The Collection",
    answer: "An underground nightclub",
    options: [
      "A suburb house",
      "A swimming pool",
      "A parking lot",
      "An underground nightclub"
    ]
  },
    {
    category: "Slasher",
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who is Texas Chainsaw Massacre based on?",
    answer: "Ed Gein",
    options: [
      "Charles Manson",
      "Ed Gein",
      "Ted Bundy",
      "Jeffrey Dahmer"
    ]
  },
    {
    category: "Slasher",
    numb: 5,
    question: "In Scream, what does the killer ask on the phone?",
    answer: "Do you like scary movies?",
    options: [
      "Knock knock?",
      "Are you alone?",
      "Do you like scary movies?",
      "Can you see me?"
    ]
  }

];

let questions3 = [
    {
    category: "Monsters",
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the name of the spaceship in Alien?",
    answer: "Nostromo",
    options: [
      "Provolono",
      "Nostromo",
      "Sualoco",
      "Bambino"
    ]
  },
    {
    category: "Monsters",
    numb: 2,
    question: "Where does Cloverfield takes place?",
    answer: "New york",
    options: [
      "Boston",
      "Los Angeles",
      "Philadelphia",
      "New york"
    ]
  },
    {
    category: "Monsters",
    numb: 3,
    question: "The earliest filmed version of Frankenstein was filmed in?",
    answer: "1931",
    options: [
      "1931",
      "1951",
      "1941",
      "1921"
    ]
  },
    {
    category: "Monsters",
    numb: 4,
    question: "The Pale Lady appears in which film?",
    answer: "From Hell it came",
    options: [
      "The Thing",
      "From Hell it came",
      "Evil Dead",
      "Scary Stories We Tell In The Dark"
    ]
  },
    {
    category: "Monsters",
    numb: 5,
    question: "Where is the setting for The Thing?",
    answer: "Antartica",
    options: [
      "Greenland",
      "Texas",
      "Antartica",
      "Ecuador"
    ]
  }

];